perfectbusiness.com 2008-09-13

# PerfectBusiness - The Entrepreneur Network to Create Your Perfect Business

  * All provided personal information will be held confidential
  * We may employ encryption strategies and/or firewalls to maintain users' security
  * Users may cancel subscriptions at any time
  * PerfectBusiness utilizes cookies to customize users' Internet experience
  * Users may edit their profiles and account information at any time

PerfectBusiness is devoted to providing a safe Internet experience for our users. This Privacy Policy details what personal information will be shared and how we will preserve its security. It is understood that all users accept the rights laid out in this Privacy Policy, while PerfectBusiness retains the right to provide personal information to law enforcement agencies in accordance with current state/federal laws and regulations. PerfectBusiness may alter these policies at any time without notice. 

Any personal information provided to PerfectBusiness will be held confidential and stored in computers and databases within the United States. Internet security is of our highest priority and we will exhaust all appropriate measures to ensure its safeguard. We will use all available and reasonable technological efforts to maintain its security for our users. For example, we may employ encryption strategies, firewalls and/or password protection if deemed necessary. 

Upon registration with PerfectBusiness, users provide sensitive information (e.g., phone numbers, E-mail addresses, mailing addresses and credit card numbers). We will withhold this information from outside individuals, parties and/or companies. We may use this information to foster and promote our services and/or products, while our employees and/or merchant service personnel are appropriately trained to maintain its safekeeping. At no time will PerfectBusiness trade, barter or sell any or all of your personal data provided in confidence to third parties without your consent. 

Personalized content appears throughout the Web site to enhance our users' experience. At any time users will have the opportunity to edit their profile preferences as well as account information. 

Users have the opportunity to cancel subscriptions and/or terminate PerfectBusiness marketing correspondence at any time. 

This Privacy Policy does not extend to linked Web sites posted within PerfectBusiness.com. We ask our users to be aware of these third-party privacy policies and adhere to them individually. 

Members may outreach to non-members through various features of the Web site (e.g., messages and invites). PerfectBusiness retains this information for the convenience of our members, as they may choose to save E-mail addresses, names and other contact information. 

We provide a regular business newsletter which is distributed through E-mail. It you'd like to opt out of this subscription or decline PerfectBusiness marketing materials, please send an E-mail to [newsletter@perfectbusiness.com](mailto:newsletter@perfectbusiness.com). 

PerfectBusiness utilizes cookies to customize the Internet experience for our users; they serve as a means to track usage on our Web site. It allows for a personalized, unique Internet venture for our users. Users who manipulate their browser settings to disallow certain cookies will not be able to view certain pages on PerfectBusiness.com. Any information you have not willingly provided us will never be manipulated to verify users' personal information, nor sensitive computer data. These cookie functionalities are common among most Web sites today. 

If a statistical analysis is executed on user frequency, user identity will not be compromised. Advertisers will not have access to specific user patterns. 

Please contact us with any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy at [inquiry@perfectbusiness.com](mailto:inquiry@perfectbusiness.com), or:

PerfectBusiness  
1907 Lincoln Blvd.  
Venice, CA 90291
